I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
I want to express this emotion,
this emotion around me
that makes my mind free
Wow!
Yahoo!
Oh yeah...
That can make this emotion
Koyuki-kun...
Oh yeah...
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion around me
this emotion makes me wonder
Oh yeah...
I can't express this emotion
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion around me
this emotion makes me wonder
I can't express this emotion,
But why, today of all days,
are they doing solos?
Oh yeah...
"Live 24 'Third Stage'"
I can't express this emotion
Let's go.
Yeah! What's up?
Third stage sounds funny.
It happens a lot in an orchestra.
Nah, it can't be that muthafucker!
In that case, you can get rid of 'im.
Yeah, alright!
I can't express this emotion
Oh yeah...
-Isn't this song kinda too long?
-Mmm...
-Hey, what's wrong?!
-What's wrong!?
I will remember when I get it,
it's resting on me
-Hey, where have you been until now?!
-You have to get on stage right away!
-Geez, you always act so big, yet...
-I met up with this again and I've decided.
Decided?
Oh yeah...
Yeah...I'm not running away.
Are you gonna give me back?
Just letting you use it.
My uncle wants you to keep Lucille.
But I can't let you do that
considering the value of it.
That is my judgment.
Ryusuke Minami,
don't forget our deal.
The sky looks shady.
Now get to the stage.
"The session on that night
was really exciting."
"I thought guitarists like you
had become extinct."
"Let's play together again sometime."
"To Ryusuke Minami,
the man who has inherited
the legend of Sonny Boy."
I'm going, Aunty.
Oh yeah...
I can't express this emotion
Ryusuke-kun!
Oh yeah...
L-Lucille!
I want to grasp but never let it go,
at least my hand will find a better way...
What a weird guitar.
I wonder what kind of sound it has.
-Wow!
-Yeah!
Wowww!
I really want to be here,
from here I will take a list...
Are there...really 500 here?
I'm thinking of saving back,
one morning when I go away
Why?
People are rushing
towards the third stage.
-Come on, Malcolm!
-Malcolm!
It's all because the equipment
got wet in the rain.
I can't say when they'll be fixed.
Malcolm says he's
going back to the hotel.
That's bad...
He's only played three songs.
The audience won't be satisfied.
He has the gall to think
he can just say "no."
That's gall.
'Scuse me...Have you seen my cell phone?
This road doesn't look familiar.
It's not on the map.
It's a back street to haul equipment.
Oh...
The live concert is
about halfway...over, right?
It seems they started quite late,
so it should be okay.
But tell me...Why was the rapper
for Mongolian Chop Squad locked up?
I dunno...I wonder why...
If I didn't meet
Generation 69 that time...
...my life wouldn't been anything.
But...I don't wanna go
to the third stage!
Everyone, please take
three steps backwards.
The audience in the front is being
pressed forward and it's very dangerous!
Until everyone is safe,
we will not allow the
performance to continue.
Please cooperate!
Hah! Idiots!
This is the second interruption.
It's bad for the energy!
I wish they would cut it out!
We can't afford to
lose this challenge!
Oh yeah...
We can't afford to
lose this challenge!
Oh yeah...
I can't express this emotion
H-Hey...Koyuki's great today.
...best my hand fades away...
Too many scenes I must
slowly count it too
He's putting his life
on the line for this, too.
Oh yeah...
-Chiba-kun!
-Huh?
Oh yeah...
This emotion
I'm looking forward to
seeing you on stage. Go for it.
This emotion
Yes! I'll sing out loud and clear!
Come on come on
BECK sounds great!
Yeah...But I thought BECK
would have more vitality.
This emotion
Yeah...But I thought BECK
would have more vitality.
-Hey! Leggo of me!
-Hey!
-Move!
-Chiba-kun!
Huh?
You're late, Chiba!!
Just a tad.
Hey! Leggo!
I'm a band member!
Just get this straight!
I just came here
to end things right.
Same here.
I'm quitting the band after today.
Taira-kun! You can't copy me!
Whatever...We're losing to the main
and second stages anyway.
We'll have no choice
but to disband.
Chiba-kun made it here.
Let's do "Brainstorm."
Let's do it.
Uh!
Uh! Yeah!
You open up the door with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
If you never...
Uh! Yeah!
You open up the door with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
What's happening? Are audience
members using their cell phones
If you never change
What's happening? Are audience
members using their cell phones
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
What's happening? Are audience
members using their cell phones
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
to tell them about this live?
No, it's even more than that.
I can't believe this.
People are coming in droves.
What's happening anyway?
You open up the door with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
If you never change
"Brainstorm"!
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
Optimistic! Yeah!
You open up the door with negative aura
Ryusuke-kun...
You are amazing, after all!
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
Ryusuke-kun...
You are amazing, after all!
You say future is murky indeed...
Yay! Are you all right?
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Ryusuke-kun...
Serial Mama, Hurrah!
Open up the door with negative aura
Ryusuke-kun...
Serial Mama, Hurrah!
Open up the door with negative aura
Serial Mama?
(I can't keep up with you)
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
-BECK is the best!
-Yay!
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
If you are at a loss as to what to do.
Raise you stiff middle finger.
It will know which way the wind blows.
Don't chain down your affection,
Awaken primal feeling
Don't be numb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Boy, I wanna play the drums with them.
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Boy, I wanna play the drums with them.
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't be numb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let yourself loose
every feeling from joy to grief
...joy to grief
Go against headwind
or ride on the tailwind.
Go against...
Go against headwind
or ride on the tailwind.
Game is in your hands.
Are you crying?
How do you play?
There are times like this
in a live concert...
Follow your brainstorm!!!
When you visualize yourself at your best
and you're in a zone.
I'm sure of it...BECK's greatness
is somehow being conveyed.
What's going on?
Why is the third stage
showing on the screen?
-Huh?
-Mr. Sykes!
Malcolm is going back to his hotel!
-Goldie!
-Yeah, I'm on it.
Why in the world is the third stage
showing on the screen, eh?
To calm down the audience.
They were getting mad
that our band stopped playing.
The main stage has also stopped.
That meant we had to put
the third stage on the screen.
The live show on the main stage
started three minutes ago.
You're fired.
This increase is fantastic.
Uh-huh...Yeah, I got it. Thanks.
What happened?
This live performance was put on
the second-stage screen...
...after Malcolm's was halted.
Maybe...
It feels like a miracle
is about to happen.
Or you could say it's only natural.
I mean, this energy
is different from the others.
This crowd isn't pretending.
They're really excited.
The flower that blooms in Babylon.
Don't touch me, baby.
Those memories of you
have lasted so long
But Yoshito's song was so-so.
-Why wait until now to say that?
-Well...that's true.
This is business.
I don't care if they're good or bad.
Yoshito satisfies the demand
of the marketplace...He's perfect.
Please take three steps backwards!
This is the third interruption!
And the live performance
isn't all that exciting.
This world is so hellbent
on making adjustments!
Hmph! Greedy idiots!
Maho...Why won't you answer?
Man, what a terrible concert.
I'd have left.
Yeah...
What? The crowd's starting to leave?!
It can't be helped.
The area's drenched,
so people are upset.
It's an outdoor concert!
Of course, it may rain!
This is bad!
The rain got our equipment
and it may take time...
What?!
Err...well...
Let's see...Right now, the main stage
has a crowd of 14,900.
The second stage has 7,000.
And the third stage has 1,400...
There certainly are a lot
of people heading there.
One, two.
Typhoon! 24. 24-7.
Non-stop. Uh!
BECK. B. E. C. K.
I feel so hot!
Send you flying.
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
What a noisy crowd!
Why don't they just put up the other
performances on the screen?
The second stage is also
having an intermission!
They only have the third stage to show.
Third stage? That's Ryusuke's band.
Oh, that scary guy's band, huh?
They're really rough.
It looks like so much fun.
Where is that?
That's BECK on Stage 3.
Hmm...
Super hot me, set me on fire
Out of this world, this perfect stage
That's...them.
Spice up my flight
Eiji-kun...
I'm not holding back, check it out
Raise my hand, drink it in, and fly
Get high 'cuz we only live once
What the-!? How terrible!
I'm stripping, too!
Wow...more and more
people are coming!
Yeah, this is amazing.
Hey Koyuki...Next is "Face."
Don't make simple mistakes.
I have a request of the audience.
Let's make sure we
take care of our trash.
It's not right to make
others pick up your trash.
Koyuki-kun! I'll throw away my trash!
Me too!
And me!
Large lips in the motion
Trying to keep blaming on
As I say reason I'm late home
Find you turning, laughing and smiling
Isn't that the boy
who was in the movie?
The movie about Dying Breed?
Why isn't there sound?
We have to have
Ran-san's permission.
My sister founded this festival!
But...
-Raise the sound level immediately!
-Yes!
So that girl's gonna be dropped?
Well, that's the rumor.
Hey, the rain's letting up.
Maybe it'll clear up.
Running over sometimes
What's that?!
Feel like you leave me behind
Now you don't have to mind it
Koyuki-kun...
The big stage suits you.
Find you shining, everyday by day
Sing it up...
Sorry, girls!
Okay, this long wait
is all under the bridge!
Let's go!
Isn't Stage 3 far?
We have to run to catch
the rest of the performance!
Can you see that
people are leaving?
Yes...the power
of music is awesome.
So many people...and they're
heading for the third stage.
It just means that
Grateful Sound isn't dead.
This next song will be our final one.
I'm going to sing my heart
out for all that's happened.
For BECK, this is...
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
Ah...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Full moon sways
Smiling in my arms for all those years
In the night sky after the rain,
a star shines bright.
Next week! Slip Out.
Go get 'em!